LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
I'm a soldier - that means I'm
Both a defendant and the judge
I am standing on both ends of the flame
Rounding curves
Overtaking life and death,
I run and fight with false shadows
No matter how many threads of
deception are woven together,
The truth shall illuminate
the face of light
Save your tears for the day
when our pain is far behind
on your feet, come with me
We are soldiers stand or die
Save your fears, take your place
Save them for the judgement day
Fast and free, follow me
Time to make the sacrifice.
We rise or fall
In the end, it is true that
they requested an apology
Fortune and Longevity
from the Asian nations, regardless of
regrets that we have already expressed.
That may be especially relevant to those who
received previous century's postwar education.
While they passively observed
the war between Asia and Europe,
it is true that they fought
in the Second Vietnam War,
and the figures of this relief
fund are also quite real.
I think I've had enough.
Just think of this as taxpayer money...
I can't win against you, Chairman...
Y-You're...!
D-Don't do this, Gino!
S-save me!
P-P-P-Please!
Gino-kun!
Hey!
Is something wrong, Gino-kun?
The ride is a bit rough.
Sorry about that, Mr. Chairman.
The
Satiated
Me
How about it? Want to go to that restaurant
I talked about and try their oysters?
They're excellent.
Oh, I think I'll pass today.
Why? Is it that "real" job of yours?
You're quite the bread winner.
How pitiful...
Food is unnecessary to a
cyborg with artificial organs.
Not to mention that to a person who
has had all of his senses digitised,
eating "good" food is but nostalgia.
What?
What's wrong?
Are you getting pursued
by Public Safety again?
Er, no...
Document: Refugee Relief Fund
Automatic Donation Form
Yeah, about Nakamatsu, right?
Yeah, I heard he was dumped again.
Food product for cyborgs...
Now that I think about
it, they are also victims.
They were conscripted for the non-nuclear World
War IV, also known as the Second Vietnam War,
and they were implanted with high-performance cyberbrains
and cybernetic parts as per military regulations.
The viewpoint that war is a multinational
corporation's bazaar is an appropriate one.
It was testing ground that greatly
advanced cybernetic technology...
That's the true identity
of the previous great war.
They weren't even aware
that they were guinea pigs.
They now seem happy, clinging to their nominal
stipends and the jobs that were given to them,
even though they lost their bodies,
their families, and even their homeland.
Never knowing that it's a false
pleasure created by the virtual persona
of their cyberbrains and
cybernetic implants...
The Police Department's investigation
branch recently announced
that a particularist terrorist
organisation has claimed responsibility
for the recent series of explosions that
targeted residential refugee relief sectors.
Tomorrow's Weather
Responsibility Claimed for Series of Explosions
in Residential Refugee Relief Sectors
The terrorist organisation apparently
demands deportation of Asian refugees.
They state that their action thus
far constitute a retaliatory measure
against riots by Asian refugees and the financial
plight induced by the current refugee aid policy.
It's a bluff.
The media merely regurgitates
what the authorities tell them.
They're fully aware that it's a bluff, but the media
manipulates information and gains profit from it anyway.
That's how they work.
What the media wants and
what it's trying to do...
All you need to do is look at their
"other" side to find the answer...
Having lost even the ability
to objectify their hedonism,
they continue to laugh
at the ignorant masses.
It's clear enough from
the way that Katakura,
who is the chairman of the three
major networks, finds endless fault
with those who continue to dine
at high-end Japanese restaurants.
To say nothing of the ruling
coalition's leadership,
executives of multinational corporations monopolise
the patents for cyberbrains and cybernetic parts
that are in the senior officials
of various government agencies...
Katakura doesn't have the nerve
to state the truth at all.
What he does have is the
desire to maintain his empire.
Government Administration Offices on Fire
Above Niihama City
Government
Administration
Offices
Attacked
Live
Live Broadcast from Government Administration Offices
Niihama City
Black smoke continues to rise at the scene;
it is a vivid testimony to the extent of the attack
on the government administration office building
by Asian refugees
protesting refugee policies.
How weak.
That won't end anything.
Again, nothing will begin.
"Reset the world"...
The real enemy is the media.
They side with authorities and
proclaim their righteousness.
However, they do not know.
They do not know that one who
knows everything stands here;
that someone with a strong will who knows and
will attempt to expose the truth exists.
I must hasten this execution.
That is the mission of one who does not fear
death in his knowledge and pursuit of truth.
A Jewish writer who was prominent in the
beginning of the last century said this:
"There is no life without truth.
Truth is probably life itself."
And this is where true life exists.
Her beauty is an undeniable truth.
Her natural beauty as a single life-form...
The enjoyment of pleasure as pleasure,
and on the other hand, the courage to refuse to possess
anything except what is necessary for survival.
The very obvious fact that
she is a complete cyborg...
a physical body that cannot be separated
from an existence specialised for pleasure.
This is true beauty.
I can be certain that she is human.
I can see something within her that is trying
to protect her humanity, just like me.
Everyone else pales before
the brilliance of her psyche.
Even if one were to obtain her with money, her
will, beauty, and truth can never be owned.
Why?
No one can sully the truth,
no matter how much they brandish their authority
and attempt to toy with our feelings.
Only one knows the truth.
And I am that one.
Tomorrow.
Tomorrow,
the world will awaken to the truth!
Finally, tomorrow's the day.
As I said, tell me if you're
going to take time off!
I don't know whether this job is
your primary or secondary one,
but just be happy that you get to be
Chairman Katakura's personal pilot.
Sure, your skills are the best.
You were a hero during the War,
but there are no jobs for guys like you disabled
combat cyborgs out there in the first place!
What?
You weren't like this before.
At the time, you had enough courage
to not avert your eyes from the truth.
If it were the old you, you wouldn't have
allowed someone like Katakura to go unchecked!
Th-The times have changed!
Everyone has to live.
Have you forgotten why I've withdrawn
from the military to follow you?
Hey, are you listening to me?
You okay?
What are you muttering?
Er, nothing...
Sorry.
I'll leave that to you.
Yes, let the other side...
What is it?
Er, nothing.
I apologise about yesterday.
I took a break from
work without permission.
Yesterday?
I'm sorry for inconveniencing you.
Oh... was that how it was?
It's me again.
No, it's nothing. Sorry about the wait.
Anyway...
Dammit!
Dammit!!!
That damn bastard needs my skills,
so he just pretended like he forgot...
Bastard!
He got all high and mighty when
I decided to bend a little...!!!
so he just pretended like he forgot...
Bastard!
He got all high and mighty when
I decided to bend a little...!!!
If I put my mind to it,
my piloting could make you guys...
My mind's clear and serene.
I do not intend to begrudge the fact that I'll
be sacrificing my life for the pitiful masses.
However... even if I am to
rid this world of Katakura,
It is possible that their networks
will cover up the incident.
If that happens,
the truth will not reach the world.
In order to prevent that from happening,
I must tell someone the truth.
My wife stopped speaking to me.
That's bad.
You'll have to get her back in a good
mood by giving her a lot of "services."
Hey, what's up?
How about going drinking for a change?
If not, that restaurant you mentioned the
other day where they have good oysters...
How strange.
Did something good happen?
Well, actually...
It seems like I might have to quit the
company because of my "real" job...
So...
Oh, a promotion?
Good for you.
No, it's not like that...
Well, I'd love to accept your offer,
considering the circumstances,
but I can't today.
Oh, it's all right. No problem.
Good luck.
Yakitori
I was hauled out to war to fulfil a purpose
far from the one intended for my existence,
just to protect the
authority of a select few.
No one can understand the magnitude
of what I lost on the battlefield.
What's your business here?
I'd like to buy her with this.
Not enough.
Not enough at all...
if that's all you have.
It's not just you.
It's not just you who lost
something important in the war.
All right, we're done.
But we haven't done anything yet.
It requires an additional
fee if you want more.
Besides...
W-Wait a minute!
I even paid the membership
fee as an advance!
Manager!
P-P-Please forgive me! If you take
that, my wife and children will...
W-We won't be able to eat...
This is the Refugee Relief Fund.
Refugee Relief Fund
Now is
the time
to help
each other
Right now,
there are
3,000,000 refugees
in Japan, who
have lost their
Motherland.
I'm sorry, I'm one of the
donors to your Fund, but...
Thank you for your kindness, sir!
Um, there's been a complication... and I'd like for you
to stop the automated withdrawal from my account...
Er, hello?
I'm sorry! We are unable to
determine the nature of your request.
Er, hello?! I want you to stop
withdrawing from my account!
I want to cancel my account with the Fund!
Then, I will now go over
the sign-up procedures.
For information regarding
your application, press 1.
For information regarding other
topics, press 2.
That was the first good
win in a long while!
Oh, that national team match?
That right cross was amazing!
Yeah, it made me numb!
Why do you want to eat?
You don't need to, do you?
Why do you want to eat?!
You don't need to, do you?!!!
Why?
Why?!
Why?!!!
Why do I want to eat?!
This is not instinct!
This isn't the truth!
That sure was a surprise, wasn't it?
Yeah, to think that he'd get taken
for questioning by Public Safety...
Seriously.
I wonder if he knew...
that the guy was Asian.
Who knew?
Gino.
The two were close.
Him? No way.
You're right.
Yep, Yep.
The Asian refugee terrorist who bombed the administrative
government office building has been arrested.
Suspect
The suspect's name is Misawa
Youichi, AKA You Mintei.
He has just now emerged from the building,
flanked on both sides by a detective.
Is it a victory performance?
Wh-Why is it him...?
Shortly after his arrest, three Asian refugee aid organisations
and the Organisation for Refugee Human Rights and Compensation
called an unusual press conference,
in which they stated that his actions represent the
sentiments of both Asian and Japanese refugees,
called an unusual press conference,
in which they stated that his actions represent the
sentiments of both Asian and Japanese refugees,
who regularly suffer
unwarranted discrimination.
As such, they allege that the authorities should
make allowance for extenuating circumstances
and have made clear their intent to
pursue a reduction in his sentence.
Please take her home.
What's wrong...?
What did he... Katakura... do to you?
It's my job.
I was... looking for you.
All the time... for several days...
No, before I was even born...
Me too.
I won't let you suffer anymore.
Let's go far away, just the two of us,
to where no one can come between us.
To our own country.
But, before that,
I have something I must do.
What do you intend to do?
I have to... release the truth.
And take me along in the process?
You've fought enough.
You've won.
I hope... that's the case...
Major, I just heard from Ishikawa.
There are no connections whatsoever between
him and the serial terrorist events.
In addition, the loss of his lower body was
unrelated to combat, according to military records;
he apparently got hit with
a vicious STD while on duty.
Hey, Major! Are you listening?
Yes, I am.
His assassination plot was just a delusion.
Well, how's he doing?
Just fine.
He's one of the many people who have faint
hope and frustration towards reality.
He could never bring himself
to carry out his plan.
Excuse me... Where to?
A proletariat who is pitifully
ignorant of the truth...
Finding out a galaxy
of planets and stars within me.
Listening to each of them
and singing the same silent melody.
I've never seen such beauty
in possibility...
No smack of doubt or fear.
(Wake up)
I hear a voice.
(And show the light)
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
I see inside
(Our time is now)
see the light now ever holding me.
All the truth,
(All the truth)
All I need,
to make all this reality.
(it's inside)
The beauty within the shell.
(deep within the shell)
(within the shell)
(Wake up)
I hear a voice
(And show the light)
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
I see inside, (the time is now)
see the light now ever holding me.
All the truth,
(All the truth)
to make all this reality,
it's inside
right here within the shell.